Arwen Christian C. Ceres

Cabuyao City, Laguna ceres703@gmail.com 0929-837-9612

Portfolio: https://portfolio-arwnchrstn.vercel.app



I am an IT fresh graduate, a dedicated, motivated, and hardworking individual, interested in pursuing a career within a progressive organization where I can practically utilize my existing skills and experience.

SKILLS AND QUALIFICATIONS

- Knowledgeable in HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, React JS, Node JS (Express), MongoDB
- Basic knowledge in PHP, SQL, JWT, Github, Rest API, API testing tools (Postman and Insomnia)
- Basic knowledge in Microsoft Office
- Basic knowledge in Adobe Premiere and Adobe Photoshop
- Basic knowledge in Hardware Servicing and Software Installation
- Always willing to learn new things
- Can work collaboratively and independently
- Have a positive attitude towards others

WORK EXPERIENCE

Internship (May 2022 - July 2022)

iForm IT Consultancy

Muntinlupa City

Front-End Web Development using ReactJS

Work Immersion (Dec 2018 - Jan 2018)

Actimed Cabuyao LISP

Diezmo, Cabuyao City, Laguna

- Encoding Inventory Management
- Warehouse Repacking

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

2018 – 2022	Polytechnic University of the Philippines – Santa Rosa Campus
	BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (BSIT)
2016 – 2018	Pulo Senior High School – City of Cabuyao, Laguna
	BASIC EDUCATION CURRICULUM: K to 12
2012 – 2016	Pulo National High School- City of Cabuyao, Laguna
	BASIC EDUCATION CURRICULUM: HIGH SCHOOL

SEMINARS AND TRAININGS

- Beginners Level Backend Web Development (Node JS, Express JS, MongoDB) Bayan Academy (August 2022)
- Advanced Level Frontend Web Development Training (ReactJS) Bayan Academy (April 2022)
- Intermediate Level Frontend Web Development Training (Javascript) Bayan Academy (February 2022)
- NC II in Computer System Servicing (2018)

PERSONAL DATA

Age: 22 yrs. old

Birthday: September 9, 2000 **Religion:** Roman Catholic

Citizenship: Filipino